One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
C Block's Blazing Battle and
the Forgotten of Dressrosa!
How strong!
The contenders are getting blown away like sheets of paper!
It's Kelly Funk who is punching them!
Ra-Ra-Ra...
Ra-Ra-Ra Rampage!
I saw it! I know I did! What was that all about?!
The two became one!
Hurry up and wear me, Bobby!
Jacket Two-in-a-Coat!
Bobby was born with such a strong body, but it was wasted on him with his weak personality.
However, when he puts me on as his "skin,"
I take over his personality!
I show my fighting skills and brutality at full with his body!
I'm a jacket human who ate the Jacket Fruit!
Whether it's an animal or a monster,
once someone puts me on,
I get control over all of him!
It was over before I knew it!
Oh, you're the older of the brothers from the Flower Country!
I beat your brother in a second!
We brothers are working together and killing people for a living!
You're so pathetic!
You can't even save your own brother!
He lost because he trained himself poorly.
That's cruel.
Ra-Ra-Ra Rampage!
Isn't the martial art of the
Flower Country supposed to be strong?!
Huh?!
From the moment I became a disciple in the way of the Eight-Impact Fist,
I renounced all emotional attachment to my brother!
But...
as the 13th leader of the Happou Navy,
I will avenge my subordinate!
S...
So strong!
The Eight-Impact Fist!
Sai shows what it truly means to lead!
Nobody could stop the monster, Kelly,
but he took him down with a single kick!
Anyways, just give me back my helmet!
Charitable Donation!
I made so much money during the last two years thanks to you!
Huh? Thanks to me?
I captured dozens of prisoners
who you set free from the great prison - Impel Down!
I'm looking to catch every single one of you escapees!
"Star Clown" Buggy!
"First Son of the Sea" Jinbe!
Sir Crocodile!
The Queen of the Queers - Ivankov!
Shiliew of the Rain!
I'll hunt you all down and make a name for myself!
I wonder how Jinbe and Iva-chan are doing.
Not just you guys!
Those that didn't get announced to the public,
the super evil escapees from level 6!
From level 6?
I know where they are now!
I didn't know there were other escapees.
Damn! Why can't I hit him?!
Oops...
Give it back.
You bastard!
That hurt.
R-Ring out!
Jean the Bandit has been eliminated!
Knocked out with a single blow!
The legendary pirate - Don Chinjao head-butted him!
He's still got it after all these years!
Meanwhile, there is a breathtaking fight going on between two equally matched contenders!
They're a great match for each other!
This life-and-death struggle seems as if they're trying to
figure out which one of them is the strongest in this event!
They're both overwhelmingly strong!
No one else can compete!
The battle of willpower vs willpower!
This is a battle royal!
Yeah!
Fight!
The excitement is reaching its peak!
Go!
This is great!
Ideo!
Sai!
The whole Colosseum is keeping an eye on the fight between those two!
You can't get away now!
Garp's grandson!
You will pay for what he did to me, Straw Hat Luffy!
The sin of your grandpa that took my fortune away!
He also took away my power and the sweet memories of my younger days!
Like I said before, I don't know what you're talking about! Talk to my grandpa!
Death is too good a punishment for Garp!
He must live on with the pain of losing what's dear to him!
I guess I have no choice.
Let's do it.
Regardless of your grudge,
I can't win unless I beat you.
Let's settle this right here!
You're in the way!
Move!
The disposition of a king.
A Clash of the Color of Conquerors.
C-C Block!
There are only...
two men left!
It seems like all these famous, tough warriors have been knocked out by
the impact from the epic clash of those two men and have been taken out of the fight!
But what did we actually see?!
I didn't know you could use the Color of the Conqueror!
What kind of king are you dreaming of becoming?!
The Pirate King!
How laughable!
There are so many in the New World who can use that power!
And only a battle between you all will determine the winner!
The strongest among a legion of "Conquerors"!
That's who the Pirate King is!
Who taught you how to use that Haki?
Rayleigh!
He's still kicking?!
How annoying!
I don't even want to think about what happened in the past!
What?
Whaaat?!
Answer me, Straw Hat.
I want to forget but it's always right there in front of me!
But it's out of my reach! My treasure!
Can you imagine anything more painful than that?!
What's going on?! The legendary pirate is...
crying!
Grandpa...
I thought the plan was to let big brother advance to the final!
I'm still not strong enough.
Nobody can stop him once he's at it!
"Chinjao the Drill."
That's what they used to call me, but not anymore.
Answer me!
Do you know what Garp has done to me?!
I told you that I don't know!
Go Lucy! Now's the chance!
Luffy-dono!
Sanji-dono, I want to get to the Toy House to rescue Kanjurou already!
I wanna help you with that but you have to wait.
We have an urgent situation here.
Look how many Marines there are around the Colosseum.
Why are there so many?
It seems like pirates and criminals are freely entering this competition.
The Marines are here to catch them as they come out.
Well, criminals should be caught.
Don't forget that you were on our pirate ship!
We need to get word to Luffy about this,
but the entrance for the competitors is completely closed off.
What's going on here-dara?
Has no one come out from the Colosseum yet-dara?
No, sir. Not yet.
There must be hundreds of losers from A-Block and B-Block-dara!
Why hasn't even a single one of them come out-dara?
It's strange.
Vice Admiral Maynard went undercover as a competitor
Marine Headquarters Vice Admiral
Shark Cutter Bastille
but we haven't had any contact with him for a while.
Why did he do that on his own?
That punk!
Is something going on...
in the Colosseum-dara?
Here in Dressrosa, there are two laws...
that people must obey strictly...
since Doflamingo ascended to the throne 10 years ago.
First, curfew is at midnight on the dot.
Citizens must not go out after that.
What?! Even adults?!
Humans have to go back to their homes
and toys have to go back to their toy houses.
No one's allowed to go out after midnight.
You can't even go for a drink!
Everything is closed anyway.
Second,
toys must not enter human's houses
and humans must not enter toy's houses!
What?!
It looks like they're friendly with each other
but that's prohibited?!
But if that's the sad boundary between artifacts and living things, it can't be helped.
Well, come to think of it, I'm kind of getting used to it already but...
what kind of toys are you guys?
You have free will and you can talk.
Whoever made you all must be a genius like Vegapunk.
Who was it?
Somebody, call the police!
What's going on?!
Please! Let go of me!
Esta, it's me!
The toy's broken! It's got "human disorder"!
Listen to me! It's not that!
Don't you remember, Esta?!
It's me!
Get away from me! You're freaking me out!
What happened all of a sudden?!
You've been friendly with her until now!
Please! Try to remember!
Get away from her!
Come with us!
Damn!
Esta! I'm your boyfriend!
Don't hook up with that bastard!
Please remember me!
Let go of me! Dammit!
Calm down!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
No! Let go of me, you bastards!
I'm a human!
Let me ride you, Onepoko!
No-wan! You're too heavy now-wan!
Onepoko!
I'm not heavy! Onepoko!
Let me go talk to him.
Don't worry. He's a toy, too.
Well, yeah, a half of me is.
Hm, Onepoko's got it!
Who are you?
I'm that boy's father. And that woman is my wife.
My name is Milo, not Onepoko.
Hey boy, don't you have a daddy?
Huh? No, I don't!
Do you have a husband?
No, I don't. I'm not married.
It's not so unusual, is it?
Bye bye!
Hey soldier, what do you want to show me? What's going on here?
What I wanted to show you is...
... this country is filled with both the forgotten
and those who have forgotten them!
All of us toys were once humans!
What?!
A Devil Fruit user who Doflamingo brought 10 years ago,
turned us all into toys!
Hey! That means you were...
There!
I see the Flower Field! I'll tell you everything there!
Green Bit
You have no mercy!
I'm all thumbs so...
Why is she not picking up?! Nami-ya!
I'm calling the right number!
Underneath Green Bit
Tontatta Kingdom
It's Usoland's Haki!
Without tension rods the shelf will fall over.
Leo, are you ready to go? Do you need lunch?
Grandma, I'm sure there will be something to eat at headquarters.
Yeah?
Grandma!
I know, I'm gonna sew up everything that might fall over!
Okay, now it's safe!
I can't believe how powerful the hero is!
He can shake up the whole kingdom with the thing called Haki!
That's right!
Because Usoland is the legendary hero!
By the way, Leo, I won't fall over even though I look weak.
Tontatta Kingdom, huh?
What kind of relationship do they have with the Warlord Doflamingo?
Whatever it is, they're serious about fighting him.
Oh, Usoland and Robiland, have you eaten enough?
Yeah, I'm totally stuffed...
I mean, I had enough and I'm ready to go!
Look, my body is trembling with excitement and making the ground shake!
How awesome!
He's unbelievable!
By the way, Leo, you people keep saying "fight" but...
... why do you wanna fight Doflamingo?
What?
The hero's very funny!
We want to rescue our 500 friends who are being forced
to work at the dark factory, of course!
What?! A factory?!
Is that the one that Luffy and the others went to destroy?!
Is that the one that's manufacturing SMILEs?
I don't know what they are making there,
but they also have the Tontatta Tribe's...
... obnoxious, selfish, mean, moody, short-tempered Princess Mancherie, too.
So we have to get going!
Don't you think you would be better off not rescuing her?
Yes, but...
... she's one of us too!
Noland would save everybody who's in trouble, wouldn't he?
What?!
Y-Yeah, he would! That's what a true hero does!
Since I'm his descendant, I'd do the same, of course!
That's our legendary hero!
Leo!
Flapper!
Leo, I just heard the Donquixote Family at the palace is on the move!
They're probably heading to the basement of the Colosseum!
Kabu-san's Yellow Cub and Bian's Pink Bee
are ready to take off anytime!
Okay!
Let's go! Usoland! Robiland!
The battle will take place in Dressrosa!
Underneath the Colosseum!
At the dark factory!
Everybody, let's go!
Yeah!
Translation & initial timing, Tsuki, Yibis (Opening)
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, Crunchyroll